小姐  我吃完了[受够]
Miss, I'm done here.
我早受够这里好几年了
Oh, I've been done here for years.
你有看见我敲锣打鼓昭告天下吗
You don't see me getting a parade.
我们这里貌似停电了
Oh, looks like we lost electricity.
冰箱里的食物这下要坏上加坏了
Uh-oh, all the food in the refrigerator will go worse.
我发现我现在
Is it a bad sign that
比平常看得更清楚  是不是不对头
I can actually see everything better?
我们终于找到让食物看起来能吃的正确光线了
Well, we finally found lighting that made the food look edible.
这里几乎暗到卡洛琳
Yeah, it's almost dark enough for Caroline
会同意在这里做爱了
to agree to have sex in here.
麦克斯  你在灯光下看过蛋蛋吗
Max, have you ever seen balls in light?
实在不好看啊
They're not pretty.
大家别紧张
Nobody panic!
整栋楼都停电了
The power is out in the whole building.
我们这里比老头乐队的演唱会还没"能量"了
We've got less energy than a Steely Dan concert.
阿憨  你看起来就像
Han, you look exactly like
《布偶奇遇记》节目里的工人
a Doozer from "Fraggle Rock" right now.
我们得保护餐厅安危
All right, we've got to keep the diner safe
以免有流氓与趁火打劫的人
from hooligans and looters.
你们还得"上"班
You're still on the clock!
你也踩我脚"上"了
And you're on my foot.
抱歉  厄尔  黑灯瞎火看不见黑...
Sorry, Earl, I can't see you in the dark....
绝不是因为种族歧视
But not in a racist way.
我在光下也看不见你呢
And I can't see you in the light
绝对是因为你矮冬瓜
in a short way.
阿憨  谁会想趁火打劫这餐厅啊
Han, who would loot this diner?
除非有人特别想打劫走"失望"这种东西
Unless they're looters looking specifically for disappointment.
麦克斯
Max?
我只是想把这伏特加
Just taking this vodka
与收银机拿去安全的地方放
and cash register to a safe place.
我们的新甜品酒吧在施工当中
Our new dessert bar is under construction
还没到完工阶段
and it's not quite there yet.
就像我撒谎说寄出还卡的钱"还没到"一样
Kind of like the credit card bill I lied about mailing,
但我选了你们两位
but I've chosen you two
当我们头两名参观者
to be the first to get a preview.
她邀请了其他人  但都被拒绝了
She invited other people. They said, "No."
她跟我保证会有糖果[无知少女]吃
She told me there would be some hard candy.
里面最好真的有
Better be some hard candy.
我里面有薄荷糖
I have peppermints inside.
那一切好说
Then we're fine.
虽然现在看起来还没什么
So it doesn't look like much now,
这里将令人眼睛一亮
it's gonna be gorgeous.
就像金·卡戴珊的丑妹妹
Like Khloe Kardashian.
是那个男变女的那个吗
Is that the one that's a dude now?
好了  我的糖呢
Okay, where's my treat?
了不起啊
Impressive,
而且几乎没从餐厅偷东西
and you've stolen almost nothing
就装潢成这样了
from the diner to do this.
等等  为什么我的运动衫变成了油漆抹布
Oh, wait, I see my sport coat is being used as a paint rag.
那是你的衣服啊
That coat's yours?
我还以为是一只导盲吉娃娃的衣服呢
I thought it belonged to a service Chihuahua.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
帅气可口  好"玩"到停不下来
Hubba, hubba, hot stuff.
如果姐还单身
You know, if I were still single,
就让你补我的"洞"
I'd let you spackle my hole.
你听到她说的了吧  小帅哥
You heard what she said, beefcake.
我不是基佬
I'm not gay.
我只是特爱性骚扰
I'm just very pro-harassment.
我为你们感到骄傲  姑娘们
I'm proud of you, girls.
你们正在努力圆梦
You're making your dreams come true,
也在为我圆梦
and my dreams, too,
前提是我在这里也能赊账
assuming you'll allow me to start a tab here.
而且不还钱
I'll never pay.
所以你在餐厅也是赊账不还钱吗
Does this mean you're not paying your tab at the diner?
厄尔
Earl?
他想开溜时就能健步如飞
He walks fast when he wants to.
我也得撤了
I gotta get going too.
我们刚看完妇产医生
You know, we just came from the baby doctor,
他让我"床上待补"
and he put me on bed rest.
一开始我还以为医生是说"床上逮捕"
At first I thought the doctor said, "bed arrest,'
这是我最爱的床上游戏之一
which is one of my favorite games.
苏菲  没事吧  你还好吗
Sophie, what's wrong? Are you okay?
怀胎五个月
Well, I'm five months along,
我的孩子已经6.8公斤了
and the baby already weighs 15 pounds,
所以医生有点小担心
so the doctor's just a little worried.
担心孩子会掉下来
He's afraid it'll fall out
就像西瓜太重  压破塑料袋掉下来
like a watermelon through a plastic grocery bag.
来吧宝贝  回家把你弄床上
Come on, baby, let's get you in bed
再把你双腿抬起
and get your legs up.
真不敢相信这一切居然不是为了做爱
I can't believe none of this has to do with sex.
敲敲门  是兰迪
Knock, knock. It's Randy.
我有六块肌[瓶装]
I got a six-pack...
还带了点啤酒来
And I brought some beers.
谁想来一瓶温潮的便宜啤酒
Who wants some warm, wet, deli beer?
这就是为什么你是最佳男友
This is why you're the best boyfriend ever.
温暖潮湿的便宜啤酒就是我的个性代表饮料
Warm, wet deli beer is the official drink of my personality.
兰迪  你看看
So, Randy, look.
你觉得这新的酒吧空间如何
What do you think of the new bar space?
我有个跟酒吧有关的问题
I've got a bar-related question.
你这里怎么放得下吧台
How you gonna fit in the bar?
蓝图上都有啊  你看
It's all right here on the blueprints, see?
吧台在这边  留下10英尺[3米]的空间
The bar goes here, so that leaves ten feet
可以放咖啡桌与正门通道
for the cafe tables and the front door entrance.
你看到这个10了吗
Uh, you see this number ten right here?
它后面有两个破折号
You see the two dashes after it?
这代表英寸  不是英尺
Those are inches, not feet.
你只有10英寸[25公分]
You got 10 inches.
人生第一次听到10英寸长而感到失望
First time I've ever been disappointed with 10 inches.
我这辈子再也不会到分类广告网站的
Well, that's the last time I get an architect
"偶遇约会"栏目找建筑师了
from the "Casual encounters" section of Craigslist.
隔壁披萨店的女人又在拍回我们墙了
The lady from the pizza place next door is banging back again.
他们应该少关注点我们的事
Yeah, they should pay less attention to our business
多注意自己的生意
and more attention to their own.
他们的披萨油[石油]多到
There's so much oil on their pizza,
美国政府可能会想出兵打下来
the U.S. might invade it.
我觉得"温啤"已经不够了
You know what? I think we've just blown past "warm beers."
我去给咱们弄威士忌
I'm gonna go get us some whiskey.
喝完波旁威士忌  10英寸会看起来大许多
10 inches always looks a whole lot bigger with bourbon.
天啊  麦克斯  我们需要更多空间
Oh, my God, Max, we need more space.
对啊  我们之间太黏  都没有私人空间
I know; we spend way too much time together.
能不能别那么吵  小蛋糕婊子们
Enough with the noise, cupcake bitches.
你们能不能别这么吵吵闹闹了
You gotta stop with this freakin' racket already.
冷静啊  吉娜
Calm down, Gina.
怎么  我是意大利人
What, 'cause I'm Italian,
所以名字就叫吉娜这类的吗
my name's gotta be Gina?
我叫安吉
It's Angie.
吉娜是我中间名
Gina's my middle name.
我还以为你中间名是"整天啪啪拍"呢
Oh, I thought your middle name was "Bangs a lot."
安吉  我们在扩建店铺
Angie, we're expanding our shop,
而且我们有施工许可啊
and we have a permit for the construction,
所以完全合情合理合法
so it's above board.
没错  我自己都很惊讶
Which, yes, even I'm surprised about.
你有毁了我生意的许可证吗
You got a permit to destroy my business?
旁边整天吵吵闹闹
Nobody wants to eat pizza
谁会他妈想吃我的披萨啊
next to this constant freaking racket.
你他妈啥意思呢
What's your freaking point?
麦克斯  我不知道你还会说意大利语啊
Max, I didn't know you spoke Italian.
跟我过来
Follow me.
来看看你们造就的地狱般生活
I want yous to see the hell you're making.
确定一定以及肯定拒绝
Um, that's a firm pass.
-我请你们吃片免费披萨  -好
-I'll throw in a free slice. -Okay.
你们看
See?
看你们在隔壁敲敲打打
See what you're doing to our office
对我办公室造成的后果
from all that banging next door?
这里要被你们毁了
You're destroying it.
这里那么强烈的一股
Uh, look, you can't destroy a room
"挟持人质"气质  谁能破坏得掉
that has this strong of a "hostage basement" vibe.
墙壁裂了  墙上石膏拼命掉
You got cracks, and falling plaster,
我跟我弟都受不了了
and my brother and I are fed up.
对吧  安吉洛
Right, Angelo?
他说"对"
He says, "Right."
我跟他是双胞胎
He's my twin.
我们用心电感应交流
We agree with our minds.
安吉  我们什么时候能吃到免费披萨
Um, Angie, when do we get that free slice?
不是想催你  但约定就是约定
Not to be pushy, but a deal is a deal,
而且我今天能吃碳水化合物
and today's a carb day for me.
我艹泥马
What the frig?
我为高中同学会刚弄的头发
I just got my hair cut for our high school reunion.
现在都毁了
Now it's ruined.
这里他妈都成战区了
It's a frickin' war zone in here!
要不是当年没钱好好安葬
My father would be turning in his grave
不然我爸都要在坟里气翻身了
if we'd been able to give him a proper burial.
你们打算怎么弥补这事
How you gonna make this right?
安吉与安吉洛
Look, Angie and Angelo,
很抱歉给你们造成不便
we're sorry about the inconvenience,
但施工只要再一周就好了
but it'll just be another week of construction.
我们保证会尽量减低噪音
We promise to keep the noise down to a minimum.
对吧  麦克斯
Right, Max?
她也用意念同意了
She's agreeing with her mind.
我就过来看看有没有什么问题
Hey, just came by to see if everything's okay,
顺便说我这辈子从没见过大卫像
and to say I've never seen the statue of David
下面是用披萨遮住的样子
with a slice of pizza over his junk.
这位猛将兄是谁啊
Who's this hunk of gabbagoul?
这位猛将是兰迪  他是我...
This hunk is Randy, and he's my--
律师  他来看看我们之间有没有任何问题
Lawyer, and I'm sure he's here to make sure there's no problem.
我们之间没问题吧  安吉
There's not problem, right, Angie?
我眼前唯一的问题就是他穿着的衣服
The only problem I see now is that shirt on him.
你好  小女子安吉
Hi, I'm Angie,
但我在考虑冠你夫姓
but I'm thinking about changing my name to yours.
点赞  这的确是金句
Props, that's a good line.
安吉  你说呢
So, Angie, what do you think?
能再忍一周施工吗
Can you stand another week of the construction?
好吧
All right.
我再给你们一周时间
I'll give yous two another week,
我给兰迪面子
'cause of Randy here,
但这是我最后一次满足你俩要求
but that's the last thing I ever do for you two.
至于你个人呢  我愿意满足你任何事
You, I'd do whatever you want..
今晚以及生生世世之中
tonight and in perpetuity.
"生生世世"
"Perpetuity"?
最好不是意大利语中"屁眼"的意思
Better not be Italian for "the butt."
两位
Guys,
我有个天才般解决甜品酒吧问题的方法
I have a genius idea to fix the dessert bar problem.
如果我们能有办法说服安吉
What if somehow we could convince Angie
让我们敲掉那面墙  然后把办公室租给我们呢
to let us break through the wall and rent out their back office?
别这样
Come on!
这点子超棒
This is a genius idea.
他们的生意不好
Their business is struggling,
不如租给我们收租金
and we could pay them rent.
如果不这样  我们店里就只能
It's either that or we have to use
用玩偶屋里的迷你家具了
dollhouse furniture for the dessert bar.
其实她说得对
You know what? She's right.
的确是个好主意
It is a good idea.
你们只要想出办法能讨她欢心就行
You just gotta figure out a way to get on Angie's good side.
或许给她带一束用香烟做成的花
Maybe you bring her a bouquet of cigarettes.
卡洛琳  安吉唯一喜欢我们的东西就是他
Okay, Caroline, the only thing Angie likes about us is him,
而我们之间我唯一喜欢的东西也是他
and honestly, the only thing I like about us is him.
完美  我们跟她谈的时候
That's perfect; we should bring Randy over there
应该带着兰迪去
when we go ask her.
兰迪  不成功便成仁
Randy, this has got to work,
就请你穿上紧身的衣服
so wear a tight shirt,
耳后抹点意大利干酪勾引她
and maybe put a little Parmesan behind your ears.
安吉洛  知道你姐姐什么时候会回来吗
So, Angelo, any idea when your sister is getting back?
从地狱回来的确有些路程
Well, it is a long commute from hell.
你好啊  兰迪
Hi, Randy.
我很乐意与你亲热  但我刚做完指甲
I would make out with you, but I just got a manicure,
而我喜欢用上指甲
and I like to use my nails.
下次吧
Next time.
我们来这里  是有个生意上的提议
So we came here with a business proposition,
还带了好吃的小蛋糕
and some delicious cupcakes.
吃完盘子得还我
I'll need the plate back.
把你的小蛋糕拿走
Get those away from me!
我准备要穿的同学会裙子
I'm going to my reunion in a dress so tight
紧到能看到当时我饮酒过度
you could see the kidney Angelo gave me
肾衰竭后  安吉洛移植给我的肾
from when I had renal failure from drinking too much Tab.
首先  安吉  我跟麦克斯很庆幸
First of all, Angie, Max and I are so glad
你能挺过肾衰竭这样的难关
to hear that you pulled through from the renal failure,
但我们来这里的真正原因是...
but the real reason we're here is--
你看见兰迪了吗
did you see Randy?
听着  咱们速战速决吧
Look, let's move this along.
我们想打穿这面墙
We want to bust through this wall
租下你这个小必胜客办公区
and rent your little pizza hut here.
这事老娘说算
Well, I'm in charge,
我不会租给你们俩
and I'm not renting to yous two.
我没时间跟你们浪费口舌
I don't have time for this.
明天的同学会  我还没找着男伴呢
I still don't have a date for my reunion tomorrow,
而且压力对我的脸不好
and this stress is bad for my face.
我脸上的填充物
I already have more filler
比电视台填档期的节目"填"的还多
than a two-hour "Dateline."
安吉  像你这样的女人
Angie, how does a woman like you
怎么会参加同学会没有伴呢
not have a date for your reunion?
我不想太冒昧
I mean, not to be too forward,
但紫红色更凸显出你双眸的美丽了
but hot magenta really brings out your eyes.
你说得没错
Well, you're not wrong.
你知道什么是错的吗
You know what would be wrong?
如果兰迪不陪你出席
If Randy didn't take you
明天晚上的同学会
to your reunion tomorrow night.
你是想被我戴戒指的那只手揍脸吗
Do you want to be punched in the face with my ring hand?
知道吗
You know what?
那...
That...
真是个好主意
is a great idea.
安吉  我非常荣幸陪你出席同学会
Angie, I would be honored to take your to your reunion.
天啊
Oh, my God!
真的吗
Really?
那安吉洛怎么办  谁陪他去
What about Angelo? What's he supposed to do?
安吉洛
Angelo,
这两妞你想挑一个带去同学会吗
do you want to bring one of these two to the reunion?
她们不是我的菜
They're not my type.
可以以多取胜嘛
Two fives make a ten, right?
奥列格
Oleg!
我知道我们这里没啥标准可言
I know we don't really have standards here,
但顾客说她的牛排不应该能这样
but the customer said that her steak shouldn't do this.
那你就告诉她  不要把盘子翻过来啊
Well, tell her not to turn the plate upside down then.
我在跟苏菲视频呢
I'm FaceTiming with Sophie.
她很寂寞
She's lonely.
跟卡洛琳打个招呼吧
Say "Hi" To Caroline.
我也没有那么"寂"不择食
I'm not that lonely.
我刚把一张桌子擦得干干净净
Ugh, I just scrubbed a table.
可见老娘有多不爽
That is how upset I am.
我不该让兰迪参加那个破同学会
I should have never let Randy go to that reunion.
我也不该让巴迪·霍利上那架飞机
And I should have never let Buddy Holly get on that plane,
但你能怎么办
but what're you gonna do?
除了在脑子了一遍一遍地播他的歌
Other than play it over and over again
一播就播了60年
in your mind for 60 years.
麦克斯  当我们
Max, it'll all be worth it
为甜点酒吧争取到多一点空间  一切都值得了
when we get that extra space for our dessert bar.
为什么上帝要兰迪打造成这样
Why would God make Randy look like that
不就是为我们行方便的吗
if not to help us get stuff?
我很担心兰迪
I'm worried about Randy.
他虽然强而有力  但这女人身怀十个
He is strong, but she has the strength
饥渴熟妇的渴"鸡"之力
of ten horny women.
快来人跟我说话
Somebody talk to me.
我要无聊死了
I'm dying here.
我刚看完全八季的《活宝兄弟》
I just watched all eight seasons of "Perfect Strangers."
我...我...都快"活"腻味了
I'm--I'm just--I'm-- I'm Balki'd out.
我感觉到原力中有人转性了
I just felt a shift in the force.
是有人把那边的桌子擦了吗
Did somebody clean a table over there?
一切还好吗
Is everything okay?
她不爽是因为隔壁披萨店的安吉
She's upset because Angie from the pizza parlor next door
需要一个男伴陪她出席高中同学会
needed a date to her high school reunion,
兰迪陪她去了
and Randy took her.
真是伤心
Well, that's hurtful.
我约过安吉两次都被拒了
I've asked Angie out twice.
他们又不是真的约会  阿憨
They're not on a real date, Han.
兰迪只是试图说服她
He's just trying to convince her
把店后面那个办公室租给我们
to let us rent their back office.
兰迪在浪费时间
Randy's wasting his time.
其实得安吉的可人儿弟弟  安吉洛
It's actually Angie's delightful brother Angelo
同意签字才行
who controls the lease.
是安吉洛说了算吗
Angelo's in charge?
安吉洛"可人"吗
Angelo's "delightful"?
我超级无聊
Ugh, I am so bored
刚去德锐大学念了一个在线课程学位回来
that I just got a degree from DeVry University.
所以她故意挖坑给兰迪跳
So she tricked Randy
让兰迪主动说陪她去同学会
into going to that reunion with her?
我要去那所高中把我男人抢回来
I am going to the high school to get my man back--
天啊  我刚才的口气好像我妈啊
oh, my God, I sound just like my mother.
我们应该去那里  使劲嗲安吉洛
We should go there and sweet-talk Angelo
让他把地方租给我们
into giving us the space.
但我们"不是他的菜"
Oh, but we're "Not his type,"
真是可惜了  因为我真的很想要
which is a shame, because I really wanted some of
沉迷电子游戏的50岁老男人的钱
that 50-year-old video-game-addict money.
我们要去哪里弄1986年那种
Well, where are we gonna get tacky dresses
俗气的裙子和头发
and hair from 1986?
我可以把你们弄得像来自1986年
I can make you look like it's 1986
因为我曾在2003年的波兰生活过
'cause I lived in Poland in 2003!
你好啊
How you doin'?
吉米·韦基奥
Oh, Jimmy Vecchio!
我是麦克斯·布莱克里尼
It's Max...Blackilini.
没印象
Doesn't ring a bell.
那我呢
What about me?
我是卡洛琳
It's Caroline...
卡恰托雷
uh, Cacciatore!
我们还跟"包鞋儿"先生一起上数学课呢
Didn't we take math together with Mr. Bag-a-two-shoes?
从来没听说过这个人
Never heard of him.
算了吧
Forget about it.
安吉洛在那边  自己跳舞呢
Oh, there's Angelo dancing by himself.
丝毫不意外
No surprise there.
我从未见过运动装款的西服
Wow, I've never seen a sweat-suit tux.
安吉洛
Angelo.
我们是隔壁的麦克斯和卡洛琳
It's Max and Caroline from next door.
你可能认不出我们了
Um, you probably don't recognize us.
我也希望没人能
I'm hoping no one does.
什么  我听不见
What? I can't hear you
因为"美女警报"一直在响
with the babe alarm going off.
彼此彼此
Oh, well, same to you.
那是什么材质  毛巾料吗
What is that, terry cloth?
其实我们是来这里找你聊聊
Actually, we came here to talk to you
因为我们想让你
because we wanted to ask you
把店后面的办公室租给我们
about renting out your back office.
我们知道你才是话事人
We know you're the big cheese.
既然你人都来了
You know, since you're here,
要不咱们来热舞一番
maybe we, uh, cut a rug?
她有四个月没有剃毛[热舞]了  所以...
She hasn't cut her rug in about four months, so...
我们可以先从舞池开始
We could, uh, start off on the dance floor,
如果我们最后
and if we happen to end up
激情到了某台车的后座
in the back of an '86 Cutlass Supreme,
那就"来吧"
so be it.
"来吧""算了吧"
So be it. Forget about it.
失陪一下
Excuse us.
麦克斯  我又不是妓女
Max, I am not a whore.
但是你的发型  衣服和妆容都不同意这点
That's not what your hair, dress, and makeup say.
你让兰迪牺牲灵肉来换取额外空间
Look, you pimped Randy out for that extra space,
现在轮到自己了
and now it's your turn.
你想租下那办公室  就卖力争取吧
You want that back room, make it happen.
数到三
On the count of three,
说"打炮"
say "Sex."
你去处理安吉洛
You handle Angelo.
我已经等很久要杀
I've been wanting to kill someone
一个用自拍杆的人  她雀屏中选了
for using a selfie stick, and she is the lucky one.
安吉  黄泉路上好走
Angie, God rest your soul,
把你的爪子从我男人身上拿开
get your hands off my boyfriend.
麦克斯  你来干嘛
Max, what're you doing here?
请你告诉我那是假发
Please tell me that's a wig.
她骗你来这里陪她
She tricked you into coming here.
她才不是披萨店的话事人
She is not in charge of the pizza place.
她弟弟才是  这是我的真发
Her brother is. This is my hair.
安吉  这是真的吗
Angie, is that true?
所以我白跳了滑步舞吗
Did I do the Electric Slide for nothing?
也不能算白跳
Well, not for nothing.
我们赢了跳舞大赛第二名呢
We came in second in the dance competition.
好吧  是真的
Okay, fine, it's true.
安吉洛才是话事人
Angelo's in charge.
我爸爸觉得他才是聪明的那个孩子
My father thought he was the smarter one
因为小时候他戴眼镜
because he wore glasses as a kid.
兰迪  你一切还好吗
Randy, are you okay?
这个坏女人有没有乱摸你的"好地方"
Did the bad lady touch you in any of the good places?
对不起我说谎了
Look, I'm sorry I lied,
但不管怎么说  这是我最开心的一晚
but for what it's worth, I'm having the night of my life.
其实我高中时候并不受欢迎
Believe it or not, I wasn't popular in high school.
没跟球队的人约过会
I didn't date a football player
也没被搞大过肚子
or get pregnant.
我只想人生中当一次人生赢家
For once, I just wanted to show up a winner.
-安吉  -惨了
-Hey, Ange! -Oh, no.
是米雪儿·帕斯古奇
Here comes Michelle Pascucci.
求你们了  别揭穿我
Please, don't ruin this for me.
这谁啊  安吉吉
Who's this, Ange?
这紧紧抱着你未婚夫  好像他是
What's she doing holding on to your fiance
葬礼守夜时最后一份吃的女人是谁
like he's the last cannoli at a wake?
忘了告诉你  我订婚了
Forgot to tell you, I got engaged.
等等
Wait.
他不会其实不是你男友吧
Unless that's not really your boyfriend.
因为...  大家都知道你是说谎精
'Cause, uh, you're known to lie.
其实呢...
Well...
她没说谎
she's not lying.
他出轨跟她在一起已经好几年了
He's been cheating on me with her for years.
我有一次在意大利餐厅里抓到他们
I, uh, caught 'em at the Olive Garden.
感觉[闻到]是撕逼的时候了
I smell a catfight,
还有男人香水味
and Drakkar Noir.
撕逼大战啦
Catfight!
臭三八  你过来
Oh, come here, bitch.
-听我指挥  -好的  小心点
- Just follow my lead. - Okay, careful.
我头发花了65块弄的
I spent $65 on my hair.
我本来计划让这发型撑一周的
I was hoping not to touch it till next week.
死三八  别碰我手臂
Don't touch my arm, bitch!
我不该碰你手臂吗
Oh, I shouldn't touch your arm?
那你别碰我男人啊
Maybe you shouldn't touch my guy.
这个派对终于开始精彩了
Finally, this party's getting good.
推我
Push me back.
你刚才推我了是吧
Did you just push me?
就推你了
Yeah, I pushed you,
但推你再大力  也没你男人
but not as hard as your boyfriend
在车子后座"推"我时大力啊
was pushing me in the back of the car.
你找死  贱逼
Oh, hell no, bitch!
我说了让你别碰我头发
I told you not to touch my hair!
天啊
Oh, my God!
她居然有刀
She's got a freakin' knife!
好  我不打了
All right, I'm out,
但我饶过你
but only because...
是因为我在假释期
I'm on parole
我上次在地铁上把一个女人的刘海给扯下来了
for pulling out a woman's bangs on the F Train.
我们走吧  安吉
Let's get out of here, Ange.
我的发型乱了吗
Is my hair dented?
亲爱的  我来搞定  我包里有筷子
I'll fix it, hun. I got a chopstick in my purse.
过来  你个刚被人用完的二手货
Get over here, you sloppy second.
我有点喜欢我也有个穿着闪亮铠...
I kind of like having a knight in shining--
这是什么  铝箔纸吗
what is this, aluminum foil?
它帮我热着我胸罩里的意大利水饺呢
Well, it is warming up the ravioli I put in my bra.
麦克斯  能跟我跳这支舞吗
Max, can I have this dance?
你觉得我们高中时  我们会好上吗
So you think you and I would have dated in high school?
我读高中时
Well, when I was in high school,
你已经30多岁了
you were in your 30s,
所以...
so...
会吧  听起来合理
yeah, that sounds right.
我刚才说服了安吉洛租后办公室给我们
I just convinced Angelo to let us rent the back office.
虽然我得当他的伴  陪他去看车展
I mean, I may have to be his date to the Auto Show.
穿好一点
Wear something nice.
比如丝质上衣
Like a silk blouse
或者比基尼
or a bikini.
他想在众人面前显摆我
He wants to show me off.
我从来没来过这样的场合
I never went to anything like this.
同学会  舞会
A reunion or a prom
或者是班级
or a class.
在这些场合应该干嘛
What do you do at these things?